♪♪
This is just awful.
It is not awful, Ben.
Everything is
going to be all right.
That's what you said last year.
You said there
wouldn't be an audit.
I said I didn't think
you'd be audited.
- What happened?
- I was wrong.
About that and what else?
Ben the IRS was not satisfied
with the information we sent them,
so you're being
audited. It's no big deal.
That's easy for you to say.
The worse that will happen is
that they'll disallow a few deductions
and you'll wind up
having to pay more taxes,
plus maybe a penalty or
two, plus interest, of course.
This is so awful.
Ben.
Ben, if you recall,
I did warn you that the IRS might
find some of these deductions
just a tad too creative.
Which ones?
Like this deduction
for $2,430, for example.
What's wrong with that?
Clothing is not an
allowable business expense.
Well, what am I supposed to do,
walk into the courtroom buck naked?
This suit makes a statement.
It's like a uniform.
It's my trademark.
That suit cost you $2,000?
I got two more just like that.
Now, Ben...
And they have to be cleaned,
so I threw in my laundry
and a couple of bottles of
cleaning fluid... I spill a lot.
You got receipts?
Yeah.
Yeah, I've got
receipts somewhere.
Find them. The IRS
is very big on receipts.
Find them.
Jeffrey, how do you
think these things up?
It's my business.
- Hi.
- Oh.
- Thank you.
- There.
Edna, is Leo in?
Yes, but he's with a client.
Would you tell him I'd like to
see him as soon as he's free?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Jeffrey.
As usual, lunch was wonderful.
Dinner's going
to be even better.
Jeffrey, don't you think we're
moving just a little too fast?
7:00, Fairview Hotel.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
Can I get that in writing?
Huh?
7:00, Fairview Hotel.
My room.
I think I can
remember that part.
I'll call the auditor, and
I'll set up an appointment.
Now, you get your receipts
together and stop worrying.
My clients get
audited all the time.
See you, Ben.
Leo, can I see you
for a moment, please?
Sure.
Sit down, Leo.
- What's this?
- You tell me.
- It's a bank statement.
- Yes, that's right, Leo.
One from your bank account and one
from my corporate checking account.
Well, is something wrong?
Look at the deposits
and the withdrawals.
You've been transferring funds from
Downey & Company's corporate account
to your personal bank
account for almost a month.
I've never seen this.
Leo, did you really think I wouldn't
notice that $12,000 was missing?
Patricia, I swear to you, I
don't know anything about this.
Patricia.
Sorry. I forgot my sunglasses.
- That's okay.
- Sorry.
Patricia, this is some kind of
mistake. I am not an embezzler.
How can you deny this? It's
all right there in black and white.
I did not take your money.
I'm going to give you 24
hours to return that money, Leo.
Now, Patricia, I have been
working for you for eight years.
You've got to give me
the benefit of the doubt.
If you don't return it by then,
I'm going to call the police.
But either way, you no
longer work for this firm.
Damn you, Patricia!
I did not take your money!
Patricia, open
this door right now!
Patricia, come on.
Don't do this, please.
I said I was sorry.
Patricia?
Room service.
- Hi.
- Just put it right around there.
- All right.
Dinner's here, darling.
Uh, you can just leave it.
- She... Just...
- All right.
Can I get you to sign for that?
All right.
- Here you go.
- Wow, thanks.
Sure.
You're acting like a
2-year-old, you know.
Just call when you want
to remove the dishes.
All right.
Damn it, Patricia, you
come out of there right now!
Leo? Hi, it's Patricia.
I know it's early, but I've been
thinking about this all night,
and maybe I did jump
to conclusions yesterday.
We should talk
about this some more.
Well, how about my place
right now? Coffee's on.
Great. I'll see you then.
Hi.
Jeffrey, what are
you doing here?
You slipped off last night before I
could tell you to have a good day.
You are something.
- Yeah.
- Oh, thank you.
- Want some coffee?
- Sure. Thanks.
Good.
Hey, I took your advice. I
called Leo. He's coming over.
- Right now?
- Yeah.
I feel better about it already.
I mean, maybe it was
just a computer error.
I hope so.
What are you doing?
I don't want to leave
any fingerprints.
Well...
Oh, Jeffrey!
Patricia?
Ohh!
It's the serial
killer, isn't it?
That strangler?
Looks that way, but we
don't know for sure yet.
So what time was it when she called
you this morning, you remember?
I don't know. Uh, about
7:15, I would guess.
Did she call you over before
work like this very often?
No. Uh, she wanted to discuss
this problem we're having at work.
What was the problem?
She thought I'd been embezzling.
- Detective...
- Excuse me, guy.
Let me get through
here, please. Thank you.
Hold on just a minute, will you?
Good morning.
Good morning,
Bob. Who's the lady?
It was Patricia Downey.
She owned and ran a
downtown accounting firm.
So what do you think?
Victim number 6?
No.
She was strangled. She's
got that mark on her forehead.
My guy didn't do this, Bob.
It's the work of a copycat.
Lieutenant, we just found this
on the floor of Mr. Kasavian's car.
Mrs. McArdle?
Mrs. McArdle!
What on earth is the matter?
This drawer was full of my
receipts. Now it's full of potholders.
What did you do
with my receipts?
Receipts for what?
Taxes... all kinds of
tax deductible stuff.
Now where did you put them?
Don't you know we're recycling
paper now, Mr. Matlock?
I find anything lying around, I take it
down to the supermarket where it belongs.
No!
My receipts
weren't lying around.
They were in a big
jumbled heap in this drawer.
Now where did you put them?
Why would you keep them
in a kitchen drawer anyway?
Because it's my
house, Mrs. McArdle.
I can keep them anywhere. I can
keep them in a bathtub if I want to.
You turn a very unflattering
shade of magenta
when you lose your
temper, I hope you know.
My Uncle Francis
did the same thing.
He's the one died of a massive
stroke... Went just like that.
Come on.
You better know
where you put them.
If the same thing happens to
you, it will be your own fault.
Everybody knows you don't keep
tax receipts in a kitchen drawer.
You keep them in a shoebox.
Went just like that.
Hello.
Yeah, Leo. Leo, I
found those receipts.
You're where?
I still can't believe
the police think I did it.
I mean, I'm the one
who called them.
Well, the person who discovers the
body is usually the first one they suspect.
You say Patricia fired you, huh?
Yeah. She accused me of
stealing money from the company,
which was not true.
What are you doing?
I can't tell you how
much I hate this room.
If they'd just put up a picture
of a cow or a dog or a bird...
So you... you no longer work
for Downey and Company, huh?
Is that important?
Well, who's going
to do my audit?
Well, you just get me out of
this mess, and I'll do your audit.
In fact, I will do your taxes for free
for the rest of your life, how is that?
I mean, my God, Ben,
they think I killed somebody.
How can you think about taxes?
Well, a penny saved.
I hate to say it, Ben, but
sometimes you act like you're cheap.
And that wire they
found in my car...
I mean, whoever killed Patricia
must've been watching me, Ben.
That is creepy.
Yeah, that is creepy.
- Mr. Matlock?
- In here.
Albert Freed.
Ben Matlock. Thank
you for your time.
No problem.
So not the serial killer, huh?
Absolutely not.
I know this crime was
committed by a copycat killer.
Hmm.
Number 1, the place is a mess.
Obviously, the victim
put up quite a struggle.
The man that we're after likes
to tidy things up when he's done.
Neat freak.
That's why he uses a
garrote... No blood, less mess.
Well, maybe his other victims
didn't put up so much struggle.
His victims were
men, Mr. Matlock.
If anything, they
probably struggled more...
Which leads us to
another inconsistency.
Ms. Downey was a woman.
Serial killers rarely change the
gender of their victims midstream.
Well, how do you
know your guy is a guy?
Well, because A, it takes a great
deal of strength to strangle someone;
and B, female serial
killers are extremely rare;
and C, the so-called Southside
Strangler smokes cigars.
I didn't know that.
Neither did your copycat.
We never told the press.
What, did he leave stubs around?
Not stubs, ashes.
We'd find them in the
garbage... Imported Havanas.
There's one other thing
we never told the press.
What?
He makes a mark on
his victims' foreheads.
Yeah, the Roman numeral Il.
What he writes may be common
knowledge, but how he writes it is not.
He carves it into their skin.
The mark on Ms. Downey's forehead
was made with a blue ballpoint pen.
Again, a copycat.
Well...
I guess whoever
killed Ms. Downey
started out trying to make it look
like it was the Southside Strangler,
but then, when Leo showed
up, he thought "What the hell"
and just threw the
murder weapon in his car.
Or the D.A. is right and
your client is the killer.
No. No.
Why would he leave that
wire so you could find it?
It's not Leo. That's the
only thing I'm certain of.
Everything I just told
you is confidential.
Of course.
Well, there goes Leo's car.
It needs a bath.
Well...
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
Well, if you change your
mind, just let me know.
I'll be right outside.
Were you pretty fond of her?
Who?
Oh, Patricia? Oh, she was okay.
But you seem so upset.
Of course I'm upset.
I mean, it's the
middle of a recession,
and I just lost my job
and my health insurance
and a whole month's
paid vacation.
And what's worse, to land a new
job, I'll probably have to go on a diet.
I mean, she was a very nice woman
and may she rest in peace and all that,
but damn it, why did she have
to go and make Leo so mad?
Leo didn't do it.
Oh, yeah, right.
Wait, Edna.
7:00, Fairview Hotel.
Tuesday the 17th was
the day before she died.
Do you know if Patricia was
meeting somebody there?
Oh, probably Jeffrey Spidel.
You know, Spidel Ad Agency?
He and Patricia had
a major thing going.
Yes?
Ben Matlock is here to see you.
He doesn't have an appointment.
That's okay. Send him in.
Mr. Spidel, Ben Matlock.
Thank you for seeing
me on such short notice.
Well, it's not every day that a famous
criminal attorney drops in on me.
- Sit down.
- Thank you.
Oh.
Oh, the Jolly Food Market.
You handle their advertising?
That's one of my accounts, yes.
I went in there once.
I had an accident.
I fell over a stack
of candied yams.
The aisles are too narrow.
On television, they look
as wide as freeways,
but in real life
they're like this.
Well, Mr. Matlock,
that's advertising.
See, people don't buy
reality, they buy image.
- If they didn't, I'd be out of business.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
So what can I do for you, sir?
Well, I've taken the case of the man
who's accused of murdering Patricia Downey.
Yes, I know.
- You do?
- Yes.
As I'm sure you know,
uh, Patricia and I had been seeing
each other for almost a month,
so I've followed the
case very closely.
She was...
very special.
I don't...
I don't think the fact that
she's dead has really hit me yet.
Is that the way it was with you?
What do you mean?
When you lost your wife.
I read someplace
that you're a widower.
Yes, yes.
But that was a long time ago.
When was the last
time you saw Patricia?
It was the night
before the murder.
Did she say or do anything unusual
or seem to be upset by anything?
Well, she was...
She told me how she'd
had to fire your client,
and, in fact, she was
pretty upset about it.
She said he hadn't
taken it very well.
And other than that, it was a
very happy, wonderful evening.
Do you remember the last
night you spent with your wife?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Must have been a
good memory, then.
Yes.
Just like mine of Patricia.
Well, that's all the
questions I had to ask you.
Thank you again for your time.
Oh, no, it's...
Don't mention it.
- I can find my way out.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Yeah, I know who
Jeffrey Spidel is.
They've got a room permanently
reserved for him here.
He handles all
their advertising.
I guess it's part of his deal.
I understand you delivered dinner
to his room last Tuesday night.
That sounds right.
Was anybody with him?
How bad you want to know?
Oh, dear.
Mrs. McArdle, what are
you grumbling about?
Oh, I'm not
grumbling, I'm thinking.
Thinking what the world's coming
to... Serial killers and the like.
Oh, well, yeah.
- And you know what I think it is?
- Mm-mm.
We've lost trust
in our fellow man.
- Trust?
- Trust.
When my cousin Kevin went
away for an entire weekend
and left all his
doors unlocked...
But his house was safe?
The house was safe,
but everything in it was
gone, including the plumbing.
That's when he lost his trust.
Well, I can see that...
Oh, I don't know.
It's not like the good old days
when you could leave
things in strange places
and come back and
they'd still be there.
The trust is gone.
We've got to get back
to trusting one another.
We have to have faith in our
fellow man and not be suspicious.
Well, we certainly
trust each other.
Oh, you can count on that.
- Oh, yes.
- Yes.
You know, I forgot
to pay you last week.
Oh, my.
Oh, thank you.
Hello.
I'm at the Fairview Hotel.
Patricia was here with
Jeffrey Spidel that night.
That much of his story is true.
But all that happy sweetness
and light stuff... wrong.
I'm sorry, sir, you
cannot go in there.
I heard what he said.
This won't take a minute.
What the hell's going on here?
I've been trying to
see you all morning.
Well, I've been very
busy. I'm on a deadline.
I get the feeling you
don't want to see me.
Why would I avoid you?
You go to the Fairview
Hotel all the time.
Maybe you heard I was
there asking questions.
No, I did not know that.
You were there the night before
Patricia Downey was murdered.
Yes. We had a wonderful evening.
Are you sure you didn't
have a big argument with her?
Of course I'm sure.
She didn't lock herself
in the bathroom?
Where did you get such an idea?
I've got to ask where you were the
morning Patricia Downey was murdered.
I can't believe you.
I really don't
have time for this.
I hate to be blunt with you but I'm going
to have to ask you to leave right now.
Please.
This makes you
look awfully guilty.
Yes, Mr. Matlock.
I know.
See if you can dig up anything
that might tell us what she and
that Spidel were arguing about.
If you can't find anything in her
office, start poking around his.
Oh, speak of the devil.
Good morning.
- Hello, Mr. Spidel.
- Hi.
Hi. Jeffrey Spidel.
Conrad McMasters.
Oh, good grip.
Let me guess... you must
be the investigator, huh?
You sure know your handshakes.
Well...
Listen, I just wanted to apologize
for my behavior yesterday.
I guess Patricia's death has had
more of an effect on me than I realized,
and I'm way behind
schedule at work.
And I guess as a result,
I'm just a little bit uptight.
- I'm very sorry.
- That's okay.
So this is where you live, huh?
Yeah, that's it.
Well, considering it belongs to a man
who by all accounts is very wealthy,
- it's quite...
- Small?
Deceptive.
Rather than letting people know
who you are or what you're all about,
you'd rather keep them guessing,
wouldn't you, Mr. Matlock?
Most people just call me cheap.
Well, in any case,
I'm just the opposite.
I make big bucks, and I want
everybody to damn well know it.
Yeah, well, that's a fine car.
Yep. Thank you.
Listen, if you need someone
to corroborate your story
about why your client was at
Patricia's house that morning,
- I'd be glad to help out.
- What do you mean?
Well, Patricia mentioned
to me the night before
that she was having second
thoughts about firing Leo,
and I told her that I thought she should
meet with him first thing in the morning.
- She agreed.
- Oh.
Oh, was that before or after she
locked herself in the bathroom?
It was just a thought.
What the hell
was that all about?
Did you notice how
dirty his car was?
Like it had been
sitting out in the rain?
We haven't had any rain.
Maybe under a sprinkler.
Have you got him? Did you
get the real strangler yet?
I'm zeroing in, Mrs.
McArdle, zeroing in.
It's looking good for my client.
Oh, now, isn't that a fine thing you're
doing getting an innocent man off.
It's just a darlin' thing
you're doing. Just darlin'.
I'm just doing my job.
You know, I once saw a
movie with Lionel Barrymore
where he was defending an
innocent man accused of murder.
Of course, you
don't have his looks,
and he had this strong
chin that you don't have
and a booming voice
that you don't have
and he was taller than you, with
that handsome Barrymore face.
And when he finished his
speech and his client was freed,
the people in the courtroom
all got up and cheered.
Oh, I know you're going to do
well in that courtroom, Mr. Matlock,
- and I do wish you well.
- Oh, thank you, Ethel.
But you're no Lionel Barrymore.
How long had you known
Patricia Downey, Mr. Spidel?
For close to a month.
How would you describe
your relationship?
We had become lovers.
Hmm.
When was the last
time you saw her?
The night before she was killed.
Did you spend
the night with her?
No, sir. We just had dinner.
She was... She
wanted to get home
so that she could meet with
Mr. Kasavian the next morning
- before she went to work.
- Oh.
Yeah. Yeah.
Are you sure it wasn't because
you had a big fight with her?
We did not have a fight.
Mr. Spidel, Mr. John
LeFort, the waiter
who brought your room
service to the Fairview Hotel,
is ready, willing
and able to testify
that he witnessed an argument
between you and Patricia Downey.
Well, if he did, he'd be perjuring
himself. I can't imagine why he'd do that.
Are you saying you did not have
an argument with Patricia Downey
in your hotel room that night?
Patricia wasn't even in
my hotel room that night.
Oh, come on!
The hotel records show that you
registered and ordered dinner for two.
Yes. Yes, sir, I did
order dinner for two,
but that's because Patricia was supposed
to meet me at the hotel at around 7:00,
and at just about 6:30, right after
the room service was delivered,
I called Patricia at her office.
She was very upset
about Mr. Kasavian,
and so we decided to
meet at Gardeno's instead.
That's her favorite restaurant.
I'm sure the hotel has
records of the phone call.
You were seen in Room
1737 at the Fairview Hotel.
You were seen having an
argument with Patricia Downey,
a woman who was found
murdered the next morning.
Mr. Matlock, I defy
you to find one person
who saw Patricia at the Fairview
Hotel the night before she was murdered.
And if your waiter says
he saw her, then he's lying.
She went straight from
her office to Gardeno's.
I met her there at
7:00. We ate dinner.
I stayed till about 9,
and then we went
our separate ways...
Forever, as it turns out.
As a matter of fact,
I have a photograph
that Reggie Lambert sent to me.
He was the maitre d' at
Gardeno's that evening.
Now, that... that's a picture of
the chef and me and Patricia.
Now, he or the chef or any of the
people sitting near us, for that matter,
can testify to the fact that we were
there that evening and we never argued.
Is that all, Mr. Matlock?
No!
No, it's not all.
Where were you between 7 and 8
the morning Patricia was murdered?
Objection.
This line of questioning
is at worse irrelevant
and at best
purposely distracting.
As far as we know, this witness was
the last person to see the decedent alive.
His testimony is not only
relevant, it's critical, Your Honor.
Overruled.
Please answer the question.
- I was at home.
- Yeah.
Tell the court what
kind of car you drive.
Well, actually, I have two.
One is a blue Blazer four-by-four
which I use mainly for recreation,
and the other is a black
Jaguar XJS convertible,
and that's the car I
drive around town.
Did you ever spend
the night at Patricia's?
Sure. Lots of times.
Parked your car in the garage?
No, I had to leave it out.
There wasn't room in the garage.
You know Millie Dumas?
No.
She lives across the
street from Patricia.
She's sitting right over there.
And she's all set to testify
that she saw your car parked
in front of Patricia's house
at 7:15 the morning
she was murdered.
That's not possible.
She knew it was your car because
she had seen it parked there so often.
It couldn't have been my car.
A black Jaguar XJS convertible parked
right on the street, just like always,
by one of Patricia's
water sprinklers.
That was your car.
You parked it there,
then you went inside, and
you killed her, didn't you?
My car was in the
shop that morning, sir.
What?
My car was in the shop
that morning getting serviced.
They picked it up the
day before the murder.
They returned it
to me the day after.
Call Doug Harding Motors.
They keep records, too, you know.
I have no idea why he
came after me like that.
It was totally uncalled for
and, frankly, a little pathetic.
Where did you get your information?
Do you think it was set up?
What are you going to do now?
Did you check the
license plate number?
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
Lousy.
One more question, please, sir.
That's great. I appreciate it.
There's my leaky faucet.
You think Jeffrey Spidel's
the Southside Strangler?
Uh-huh.
- And that he murdered Patricia Downey?
- Yep.
All because Conrad found
cigars in his hotel room?
They were imported Havanas.
- Ben, that's no proof.
- I know.
That's the reason I need to see
your files on the other murders
so I can get some proof.
Why would he make the Downey
murder look like a copycat?
I don't know.
I have never known of a serial
killer who was his own copycat.
Never.
You have never
known Jeffrey Spidel.
He doesn't fit the profile.
Doesn't matter. He's the one.
- You sure this isn't just sour grapes?
- I'm sure.
Okay.
Now, I want that back
first thing in the morning.
Hmm.
I have no idea why he
came after me like that.
It was totally uncalled for
and, frankly, a little pathetic.
Where did you get your information?
Do you think it was set up?
What are you going to do now?
Did you check the
license plate number?
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
Lousy!
Did you check the
license plate number?
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
Lousy.
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
Lousy!
How does it feel to make a
fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
Lousy!
- Make a fool of yourself, Mr. Matlock?
- Lousy!
Ben?
In here.
What are you reading?
Everything I can on
the Southside Strangler.
He kills successful people:
Councilman Mendez, Bill Davis,
Warren Daniels, and now Patricia.
Well, when you're through with that,
here's everything on Jeffrey Spidel.
Yeah?
You and Mr. Spidel have
something in common.
- What?
- He went to Harvard Law.
Yeah?
- But he flunked out.
- Huh.
Hey, if you don't need anything
else, I'm going to go home, okay?
- No, go ahead.
- I'll see you later.
Right.
Hey, Conrad?
Hey... Hey... Hey, Conrad!
Let's talk, Mr. Matlock.
Okay.
You presented a great challenge,
so pardon me for wanting
to savor the moment.
Saw the news.
The legendary Ben Matlock really
got cut down to size today, didn't he?
Being humiliated like
that really hurts, doesn't it?
And you know something?
The pain never goes
away. It never goes away.
Every time you look in the mirror, it comes
right back at you like a kick in the gut.
You're never quite the same.
You set up that whole copycat thing
just to embarrass me in the courtroom?
Well, actually, I first
got the idea when I
heard that Leo was
going to do your taxes.
And so I started
dating Patricia,
and I transferred a
few funds by computer
so it would make Leo look like he had
been embezzling, and the rest you know.
I was very sure that you
would be representing him.
As I said, it was
quite a challenge.
Councilman Mendez
and Bill Davis,
you humiliated them
before you killed them.
Put them out of their misery
is a better way to put it.
They were both lawyers.
Very good.
That mark on your forehead
wasn't the Roman Numeral Il?
No. No, it's Greek...
uppercase Pi.
Plaintiff.
A little touch of irony.
No more talk.
Why lawyers?
Why not?
More fun.
Police officer!
Stay right where you are.
I guess...
I guess you thought I'd never
know you were coming for me.
But I pretty well had the
whole thing figured out.
What do you mean you'd
be lucky to charge him?
He tried to kill me.
All right. We can charge him
with attempted murder, yes,
but as for all those other
murders, Ben, I'm telling you,
we're going to have
to be real lucky.
Oh, come on. He practically
confessed last night.
All right, wait a minute, okay?
Now just listen.
You humiliated them
before you killed them.
Put them out of their misery
is a better way to put it.
He didn't actually
confess to anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
In order to indict
him for murder,
we'd have to have solid evidence
he's the Southside Strangler.
And the way this guy covers his tracks,
I'm telling you, it's going to be tough.
This is just great.
You can't prove him guilty, and
I can't prove my client innocent.
I don't know what to tell you.
Wait a minute.
Let me check something out.
That's a nice outfit,
Mr. Spidel. What's the occasion?
Mr. Spidel's arrest is not
relevant to this trial, Mr. Matlock.
Please confine your questions to those
that are germane to these proceedings.
Sorry, Your Honor.
Just a couple of questions,
and then you and your friend
will be free to go, so to speak.
- Mr. Matlock.
- Sorry.
Where were you between 7 and 8
the morning Patricia
Downey was murdered?
I've already testified
that I was at home.
I remember. I remember.
And Millie Dumas
has just testified
that she saw a black
Jaguar XJS convertible
parked in front of her house
the morning she was murdered.
Was that your car?
No.
I told you my car was in the
shop that morning, Mr. Matlock.
Let me rephrase that question.
Was that a car you had rented?
No.
No?
The loaner that the dealership
gave me was maroon.
I'm not talking about that car.
I'm talking...
about this car...
The car you rented from the Top of
the Line car rental agency in Savannah.
See?
This is a copy of
the rental agreement.
There's the imprint
of your credit card.
There's your signature.
You rented it the night before
and took it back the next day.
Now, like you say, the
dealership gave you a loaner.
Why do you need to go
out and rent another car?
Why do you go all the way
to Savannah to do it, huh?
The car you drove by
my house the other day...
That was your car,
now out of the shop.
You put water spots on it yourself
to make me think it was this car.
You wanted somebody
to think they saw your car
parked in front of Patricia's
house that morning, didn't you?
Just like you wanted
the waiter to think
he witnessed a fight
between you and Patricia.
It was all part of your big plan to make
me think that I had you dead to rights
and then at the last minute you'd
yank the rug out from under me
and make me look like a
number A-1 jackass, didn't you?
But all the time, I
knew you were the one.
It took me a while to find that
car rental agency, but I found it.
It may take the police a while
to place you at Councilman Mendez'
home the night he was murdered,
and Bill Davis' home the
night he was murdered,
and all the others.
It's just a matter of time
because if you made one
mistake, you made others.
I guess the day the
IRS decided to audit me
wasn't exactly your lucky
day, either, was it, Mr. Spidel?
www.tvsubtitles.net